Back To Main

[

(212) 812-5240](tel:+12128125240)

            Local movers just around the corner.

            Smooth and easy moving across the map.

            Long distance movers that go the extra miles.

            Move you all around the world.

            A nicer way to move your business.

            Your city’s perfect move.

            Seamless residential moves to your dream house.

            Your stars and stripes interstate moving experts.

            Ultimate in moving luxury and convenience.

            Fine art movers for enthusiasts.

            Piano moving done in perfect harmony.

            Pool moving for superior experience.

            Ensuring secure protection during your move.

            The perfect place to store your belongings.

            More space for more memories.

            Simplify your move with secure storage solution.

            Ready when you need it most.

            Providing secure storage solutions in the New York state area.

            Delivering safe storage in Los Angeles and beyond.

            Convenient and protected top-notch storage in the Bay.

            Trustworthy and reliable storage tailored for Miami residents.

            Offering trusted premier storage services in FT Lauderdale.

            Ensuring flexible storage options for Philadelphia residents.

            Your trusted moving solution.

            The tool you need for an easy move.

            Your efficient and eco-friendly solution.

            Request your COI in just one click.

            When advanced technology meets piece of mind.

            Protect your items and move with confidence.

        * 

        * 

        * 

            Serving the vibrant New York state region.

            Moving the diverse Florida community and beyond.

            Navigating California’s moves with excellence.

            Streamlining moves in the diverse New Jersey locale.

            Efficient moves in the picturesque Connecticut area.

            High quality of moving services in Philadelphia area and its surroundings.

            Learn more about the company and its origins.

            Our experienced movers change the moving game every day.

            Ready to move your career forward?

            Roadway is the Official Moving and Storage partner of the New York Yankees.

            Discover more about the most rewarding referral program in the moving industry.

            Discover our charity events and join us in making the difference.

            See what our customers have said about us so far.

            We stay up to date with all of our licenses, regulations, and technology.

            Let’s make your next big move easier.

            A nice move deserves a nice tip.

            Discover more how to move with confidence.

            Follow Roadway Moving and be up to date on the latest experiences.

            We know all the right moves.

            Experience the world of moving entertainment.

            Exciting events await, join us for memorable experiences and community celebrations.

            Need some info? We have the answers!

            Moving questions? Connect with us for assistance.

            Your opinion matters. Submit your comments here.

            Media inquiries? Contact our team for more information.

            We care about causes. Tell us how we can support you.

            Planning to empty storage? Book your move-out slot.

            Need a COI? Fill out the form for swift processing.

            Have a claim? Begin the process and file it here.
            
* Popular Search

Ready to get moving?

Choose your Roadway Storage service:

Ready to get moving?

Popular Cities

Ready to get moving?

Ready to get moving?

Ready to get moving?

Quick Links

* [Moving

    ](#)
* [Storage

    ](https://www.roadwaymoving.com/storage/)
* [Services

    ](#)
* [Locations

    ](https://www.roadwaymoving.com/locations/)
* [Company

    ](https://www.roadwaymoving.com/about/)
* [Resources

    ](#)
* [Contact

    ](https://www.roadwaymoving.com/contact-us/)

[

(212) 812-5240](tel:+12128125240)

Privacy Policy
==============

General
-------

This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for [www.roadwaymoving.com](https://www.roadwaymoving.com/).

This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this web site.

#### Information Collection, Use, and Sharing

Roadway Moving is the sole owner of the information collected on this site.

We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you.

We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us.

We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.

No mobile information will be shared with third parties/affiliates for marketing/promotional purposes. All the above categories exclude text messaging originator opt-in data and consent; this information will not be shared with any third parties.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

#### Your Access to and Control over Information

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:

1. **1.** See what data we have about you, if any.
2. **2.** Change/correct any data we have about you.
3. **3.** Have us delete any data we have about you.
4. **4\.** Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

#### Links to other Web Sites

This site may contain links to other web sites.

Roadway Moving is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other web sites, nor does Roadway Moving endorse any products or services offered by those sites.

#### Security

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page.

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

#### Updates

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.

#### Contact Information

If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, or if you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information, contact us via telephone at 212-812-5240 or via email at [\[email protected\]](https://www.roadwaymoving.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

* What We Do
    
    * * *
    
    * Featured Moving
    * Delicate Moving
    * Storage Services
    * Seamless Moving Services
    * More Services
* Locations & Service Area
    
    * * *
    
    * East Coast Moving
    * West Coast Moving
    * Storage Facilities
    * Popular Routes
    * Find Us On Social
        * [
            
            ](https://www.instagram.com/roadwaymoving/ "Instagram")
        * [
            
            ](https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCDKmQ7k9jclvjFiUrqZ3pAQ "YouTube")
        * [
            
            ](https://www.linkedin.com/company/roadway-moving/ "LinkedIn")
        * [
            
            ](https://twitter.com/RoadwayMoving "X")
        * [
            
            ](https://www.facebook.com/RoadwayMoving/ "Facebook")
        * [
            
            ](https://www.yelp.com/biz/roadway-moving-new-york "Yelp")
* Company
    
    * * *
    
    * Roadway Moving
    * Support
    * Media
    * Community
    * Get Moving!

        * [

            Get a free quote](https://www.roadwaymoving.com/full-form/)
        * [

            (212)-812-5240](tel:+12128125240)

* * *

845 3rd Ave 6 FI, New York, NY 10022

Fully licensed and insured:  
NY DOT #T-38589USDOT #1854436 ICC MC-671325 FMC #028636

© 2024 Roadway Moving Inc. All Rights Reserved.

#### Ready to get moving?

Please enable JavaScript in your browser to complete this form.

Please enable JavaScript in your browser to complete this form.

Moving from \*

Moving to \*

Get Your Quote
